To be able to use the full range of Shopware 6, we recommend activating Javascript in your browser.

Shipping within 24h

All parts are MDR compliant

Purchase comfortable on account

Customer Service: [\+ 31 88 0531000](tel:+3188 0531000)

EN

Deutsch

English

Français

Nederlands

€ Eur

 £ GBP

 $ USD

 € EUR

Search

My account

Close menu

Your account

or [sign up](https://www.medicalspareparts.com/account/login "Sign up")

* close

* close

* close

* close

* close

About MSP

We are your partner in Reliable Spare Parts

Close menu

Language: EN

Deutsch

English

Français

Nederlands

€

Currencies: Eur

 £ GBP

 $ USD

 € EUR

About MSP

You are here:

2.  [Home](https://www.medicalspareparts.com/ "Home") 

4.  [Privacy](https://msp-medical.com/general/privacy/ "Privacy") 

**Quickly go to**

Privacy
=======

MSP Group finds the privacy of our customers and visitors very important. The protection of your privacy is something we take very seriously. MSP has implemented the conditions of the General Data Protection Regulations so that we can ensure your privacy. In the following Privacy Statement we describe why we process your data, how we do it and what rights you have in this regard.

Personal data  

----------------

MSP Group processes personal data about you because you use our services and/or because it was provided by you to us.  

Here below you can find an overview of the personal data that we process:  

* First and last name  
    
* Address data
* Phone number  
    
* E-mail address  
    
* Other personal data that you actively provide, for example by creating a profile on this website, in correspondence and by telephone  
    
* Location data - Data about your surfing behaviour across different websites (for example because this company is part of an advertising network)  
    
* IP address -Internet browser and device type

Special and/or sensitive personal data that we process  

---------------------------------------------------------

Our website and/or service does not intend to collect data about website visitors younger than 16 years old. Unless they have parental or guardian permission. However, we cannot check whether a visitor is older than 16. We therefore advise parents to be involved in the online activities of their children, in order to prevent data about children being collected without parental consent.  

If you are convinced that we have collected personal information about a minor without this permission, please contact us at [info@msp-medical.com](mailto:info@msp-medical.com) and we will delete this information.

Why we process your data  

---------------------------

MSP Group processes your personal data for the following purposes:  

* Handling your payment - Sending our newsletter and/or other marketing related material To be able to call you if this is necessary to be able to perform our services  
    
* Offer you the option to create an account  
    
* To deliver goods and services to you

How long we store your data  

------------------------------

MSP Group will not keep your personal data for longer than is strictly necessary Our storage period is: 7 years. After this period we will use your data anonymously for internal  reporting.

How we track website visits  

------------------------------

MSP Group uses functional, analytical and tracking cookies. A cookie is a small text file that is stored in the browser of your computer, tablet or smartphone when you first visit this website. On the one hand, MSP Group uses cookies with a purely technical functionality. These ensure that the website works properly, for example your preferred settings can be remembered and help us to make the website work properly. This also helps us to optimize our website.  

In addition, we place cookies that keep track of your surfing behaviour so that we can offer customized content and advertisements. On your first visit to our website, we already informed you about these cookies and asked for permission to place them. You can opt out of cookies by setting your internet browser so that it no longer stores cookies. In addition, you can also delete all information that has previously been stored via the settings of your browser.  

For an explanation, see:[https://veiliginternetten.nl/themes/gedrag/cookies-wat-zijn-het-en-wat-doe-ik-ermee/](https://veiliginternetten.nl/themes/gedrag/cookies-wat-zijn-het-en-wat-doe-ik-ermee/) Cookies are also placed on this website by third parties. These are, for example, advertisers and/or social media companies.

How can you view, modify or delete your data  

-----------------------------------------------

You can easily do this yourself via the personal settings of your account. If these settings do not work or if you have other questions/comments about data processing, please send a specified request to [info@msp-medical.com](mailto:info@msp-medical.com). In order to verify your identity, we ask you to enclose a copy of your proof of identity. Make the citizen service number (BSN), MRZ (machine readable zone, the strip with numbers at the bottom of the passport), passport number and your passport photo black in this copy. This is to protect your privacy.  

MSP Group will respond to your request as soon as possible, but in any case within four weeks.

Your security  

----------------

MSP Group takes the protection of your data seriously and takes appropriate measures to prevent misuse, loss, unauthorized access, unwanted disclosure and unauthorized modification. If you have the impression that your data is not properly secured or there are indications of misuse, please contact our customer service or via [info@msp-medical.com](mailto:info@msp-medical.com)

Where are we

**MSP Medical Spare Parts**  
De Sonman 7  
5066GJ, Moergestel, Netherlands  
**T:** [\+ 31 88 0531000](tel:+3188 0531000)  
**E:** [info@msp-medical.com](mailto:info@msp-medical.com)  
**CoC:** 74554158  
**VAT:** NL859946125B01  
  
**Opening Hours:**  
Mo - Fr: 8AM - 5PM (CET)  
Sa - Su: Closed

General

Payment methods

Newsletter

Just subscribe to our newsletter and you will always be among the first to be informed about new products and offers.

Subscribe to newsletter Unsubscribe from newsletter

Email address\* 

Privacy \*

 By selecting continue you confirm that you have read our [data protection information](https://www.medicalspareparts.com/widgets/cms/bd97d78a319043d69c4241acb837f744 "Data protection information") and accepted our [general terms and conditions](https://www.medicalspareparts.com/widgets/cms/b453a7477de949b4adcb37f018d2ffea "general terms and conditions").

\* All prices incl. VAT plus [shipping costs](https://www.medicalspareparts.com/widgets/cms/19f81a5284b64e87b0449f7479aa5d5a) and possible delivery charges, if not stated otherwise.

© 2024 MSP Medical - All Rights Reserved. Theme by [ThemeWare®](https://themeware.design/ "ThemeWare® Shopware Theme")

Important Information

The items shown in this catalog are by default NOT original parts unless they are expressly marked as such. Fig. and OE no. are for comparison purposes only and may differ / All logos, brand names and trademarks used are the property of their owners. MSP does not have a commercial and/or economical link with the mentioned OEM's.
